

· Using Free CV Search you

have access to featured

directly using the email

misuse of candidate

withheld

option provided. To prevent

information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been

candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice

Important

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211





Rumana Kadri Rumana Kadri Rumana Kadri Business Analyst seeking role in Web Application Development, Business Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Process Improvement, Agile Methodology, Waterfall, Client Relationship Management, Root Cause Analysis, VB. NET, ASP. Net, Javascript, HTML, SDLC, CSS, WPF Current Designation: Business Analyst Total Experience: 8 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Company: Advanced Business and Healthcare Notice Period: 3 Months Solutions Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Information Technology] Current Location: Vadodara / Baroda Pref. Location: Mumbai.Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Maintenance Role: Business Analyst Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Married Key Skills: Business Analyst, Web Application Development, Business Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Process

Improvement, Agile Methodology, Waterfall, Client Relationship Management, Root Cause Analysis, VB.NET, ASP.Net, Javascript, HTML, SDLC, CSS, WPF

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Jump to Section Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Achievement-driven professional with over 8 years of experience

Mcrosoft Certified Technology Specialist: Web Application Development with Mcrosoft .Net Framework 4

Mcrosoft Certified Professional: ASP.NET M/C4 Web Applications

Skilled in coordinating with business units, stakeholders and technical leaders to gather and clarify business requirements; analysed corporate business processes to develop customized solutions

Proficiency in mapping business processes and studying requirements, designing, implementing and transitioning, processes as well as solutions in line with the guidelines specified by clients; effective in ensuring business functionality & enhancement of competitive advantage

On-site work experience in UK based office for training as well demo to the clients for the application Forward-focused Business Analyst, experienced in providing direction for developing processes

Work Experience

Advanced Business and Healthcare Solutions as Business Analyst Feb 2018 to Till Date

Recommending process improvements and reviewing functional requirements while developing and sustaining strong relationships with business experts

Creating user stories, getting approvals and grooming the user stories with the Development team

Liaising with UK stakeholders on any intermediate changes in requirements

Performing functional testing and participate and contribute to BA Forum as per your available bandwidth

Scaling agile framework to implement scrum at enterprise level and facilitating scrum meetings

Providing solutions to complex problems applying analytical skills

Developing analytics-driven insight modules for detecting revenue opportunities & refer to business issues Assisting in the project planning and estimation operations, implementing project development plans within the stipulated budgets; reviewing estimations using the required methodology and bottom line for delivery

Coordinating with clients to facilitate smooth communication, analyzing business requirements and offering solutions

Describing project scope, assumptions, approach, resource needs, high level timelines & commercials Developing analytics-driven insight modules for detecting revenue opportunities & refer to business issues

Reviewing functional requirements while developing and sustaining strong relationships with business experts Maintaining healthy and working relationship with clients and development team throughout contract lifecycle, escalating important concerns if required; monitored metrics to expedite desired service level, quality targets and

maximized resolution to achieve customer satisfaction

Mentoring the fellow BA's, reviewing their work and assisting in their overall development

NJ IndiaInvest - Finlogic as System Analyst Aug 2014 to Feb 2018

Strategic Alliance as Software Developer / Lead Software Developer / Client Contact Jun 2012 to Aug 2014

^ Back to Top

Education

 $\hbox{UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Information Technology) from Sarvajanik College of Engineering and Technology, Surat in 2012.}\\$

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
WPF, ASP.Net, VB.Net Web			
Javascript, HTML, DHTML, XML, CSS			
SDLC (Waterfall), Agile			
Microsoft SQL Server 2005/2008/2012			
Oracle 10g, MySQL 5.5			
Networking, SDLC			
Artificial intelligence			
MS OFFICE			
ITEXTSHARP			
Balsamiq, Awesomium ,SDK			
Axure RP 8		2020	2 Year(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Hindi				
English				
Gujarati				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.